試鏡！
禁止停車
晚9點至早六點
否則拖走
貝克先鋒
春
卡薩布蘭卡：美國經典電影 亨弗萊 鮑嘉和英格麗 褒曼為男女主角
考特 貝茜：鋼琴家，著名大樂隊領班
奇克 韋伯：著名爵士樂樂隊隊長
危險遊戲：95年上映的劇情類電影
橘子郡男孩：03年首播的美劇
路易斯 阿姆斯特丹：爵士樂壇無人不知的大人物，就好像搖滾音樂的貓王。
肯尼 基：美國著名薩克斯演奏家。
西德尼 貝謝：爵士高音薩克斯風的先驅者，以粗獷的抒情獨奏揚名。
麗都街：紐約百老匯附近的劇場區
燈塔酒吧
夏
貝克先鋒
好久不見
博爾德城
今晚上映
作者 米婭 多蘭
戴爾普拉多圖書館
博爾德城 內華達
冬
塞納河:法國北部重要河流
格裏菲斯公園:其山上有著名好萊塢巨型標牌
五年後
南加利福尼亞又迎來了晴朗而炎熱的一天
It's another hot and sunny Southern California day.
今日洛杉磯市區溫度為29℃
The temperature in downtown Los Angeles is 29℃...
夜晚將會降溫至
And at night will drop to...
#又想起那天#
#I think about that day#
#聖達菲西邊的灰犬車站#
#I left him at the Greyhound station#
#我們就此分別#
#West of Santa Fe#
#我們才十七歲 氣氛甜蜜而美好#
#We were 17 but he was sweet and it was true#
#但我仍選擇了離開#
#Still I did what I had to do#
#我知道這才是我應該做的#
#Cause I just knew#
#夏日週日的晚上#
#Summer Sunday nights#
#我們癱坐在座位#
#We'd sink into our seats#
#影院的燈光變暗#
#right as they dimmed out all the lights#
#變幻的光影 悠揚的樂符#
#A Technicolor world made out of music and machine#
#召喚著我#
#It called me to be on that screen#
#我也可以是電影的主角#
#And live inside each scene#
#名下沒有一分錢 跳上了公車就來試演#
#Without a nickel to my name Hopped a bus, here I came#
#是勇敢還是瘋狂#
#Could be brave or just insane#
#只有過後才知道#
#We'll have to see#
#因為某天在這慵懶的城市#
#Cause maybe in that sleepy town#
#他會坐在燈光熄滅的電影院裏#
#He'll sit one day, the lights are down#
#回想著在哪裏見過這女主角#
#He'll see my face and think of he used to know me#
#我在群星薈萃的洛杉磯#
#Climb these hills, I'm reaching for the heights#
#追尋著燈光與夢想#
#And chasing all the lights that shine#
#當你對一次失敗感到失望#
#And when they let you down#
#你仍然會從地上爬起#
#You'll get up off the ground#
#清晨不久就會來到 這又是陽光明媚的一天#
#Cause morning rolls around And it's another day of sun#
#峽谷的韻律每天在我耳畔響起#
#I hear'em ev'ry day#
#它們從不減退消散#
#The rhythms in the canyons that'll never fade away#
#舞廳裏人迴響著我留下的民謠#
#The ballads in barrooms left by those who came before#
#他們說你達不到我們想要的水平#
#They say: "You gotta want it more"#
#所以敲開每扇門尋找機會#
#So I bang on every door#
#即使受到拒絕 即使囊中羞澀#
#And even when the answer's "No" Or when my money's running low#
#有音樂話筒和閃亮的霓虹#
#The dusty mic and neon glow#
#對我來說就足夠#
#Are all I need#
#有時#
#And someday as I sing my song#
#一個小城孩子會來聽我唱歌#
#A small-town kid'll come along#
#那就是讓他堅持下去的動力#
#That'll be the thing to push him on and go go#
#我在群星薈萃的洛杉磯#
#Climb these hills, I'm reaching for the heights#
#追尋著燈光與夢想#
#And chasing all the lights that shine#
#當你對一次失敗感到失望#
#And when they let you down#
#你仍然會從地上爬起#
#You'll get up off the ground#
#清晨不久就會來到 這又是陽光明媚的一天#
#Cause morning rolls around and it's another day of sun#
#當你對一次失敗感到失望#
#And when they let you down#
#清晨不久就會來到#
#The morning rolls around#
#又是陽光明媚的一天#
#It's another day of sun#
#It's another day of sun Sun, sun, sun, sun#
#又是陽光明媚的一天#
#It's another day of sun#
#這就是陽光明媚的一天#
#Just one more day of sun#
#又是陽光明媚的一天#
#It's another day of sun#
#今天才剛剛開始#
#Another day has just begun#
#又是陽光明媚的一天#
#It's another day of sun#
我們都不敢相信發生了那種事
We could not believe what was happening.
我發誓 她喝醉了
I swear to God. She was wrecked.
她完完全全醉了 我知道
She was completely wrecked! I know!
我知道 那簡直太 太瘋狂了
I know, it was - it was pure insanity.
是瘋狂這詞嗎
"It was insanity?"
應該是荒唐 那簡直太荒唐了
Lunacy. "It was pure lunacy. "
有毛病麼這人 我該走了
What is his problem? I should go.
- 一杯卡布奇諾 - 好的 馬上
- Cappuccino, please. - Right. Of course.
- 不用給了 - 噢 謝謝 我還是付了吧
- On us. - Oh no thank you. I insist.
見鬼
Shit!
- 米婭 你要去哪兒 - 噢 已經過了五分鐘了
- Mia, where do you think you're going? - Oh, it's five after.
- 你明天早點來 - 好的
- You better be early tomorrow - Okay.
祝夜晚愉快
Have a good night!
她喝醉了
She was wrecked
那簡直太荒唐了 那
It was pure lunacy! It was...
太瘋狂了 我只是
It was so crazy and I just...
你差點就死了
Oh you would have died.
不 特納很好 他很好 我只是
No, Turner is fine. Turner is fine. I just uhm...
你要到了丹佛再告訴她嗎 還是
Are you going to wait until Denver to tell her, or...?
什麼
What?
好吧
Okay.
沒有 我為你感到開心
No, I'm happy for you.
真的 我為你感到高興 我只是
I am. I'm happy for you. I just...
我只是覺得
I just thought...
我不知道我在想什麼 就是
I don't know what I thought I guess it just...
暫停一下
Wait a second.
- 怎麼了 魯比 - 傑西卡打電話過來
- What Ruby? - Jessica called.
- 跟她說我會回給她的 - 兩分鐘左右嗎
- Tell her I call her back. - In two minutes?
不到兩分鐘吧
Less than two minutes.
- 我幫你帶午餐 - 我這邊快好了 謝謝
- I'll go get your lunch. - I'm almost done. Thank you.
好的 我們完工了
Oh you know what? I think we're good.
感謝你的參與
Thanks for coming in.
我的天 你要開個窗嗎
Holy shit! You want to open a window?
- 這是給你騰個地方 - 謝謝你了
- It was trying to give you an entrance. - Thank you.
米婭 試鏡怎麼樣
Mia! How the audition go?
- 老樣子 - 珍去了嗎 瑞秋呢
Same here. Was Jen there? Or Rachel?
- 我不認識什麼珍和瑞秋 - 她們差的要死
- I do not know who Jen and Rachel are. - They are the worst.
- 我不知道她們在不在那兒 - 我打賭她們絕對在
- I don't know if they were there. - I bet that they were.
你們為什麼擠在浴室裏開座談會
Why is there a convention in the bathroom?
噢對了
Oh right.
還有兩分鐘寶貝兒們 米婭你也來 對嗎
Two minutes people. Mia you're coming, right?
不行
I can't!
我要工作
I'm working.
什麼
What?
她剛才是不是說 工作
Did she just say "Working"?
- 幹嘛 - 很遺憾你今天的試鏡不是很順利
- What? - Sorry it didn't go well today.
我收件箱裏有差不多四部戲
And there's like four things in my inbox...
都非常適合你 我會幫你申請
that you're perfect for and I will submit you.
但是現在 你要和我們一起去
But right now, you're coming.
會很有意思的
It will be fun.
不 沒意思
It's not gonna be fun.
- 會的 - 不會
- It could be. - It's not.
肯定又是一群攀高枝的
It's gonna be a bunch of social climbers.
妖艷賤貨全部擠在一個大玻璃房子裏
All packed into one of those big glass houses.
這件衣服怎麼感覺似曾相識
This looks familiar.
- 我正打算還你呢 - 你拿走多久了
- I was gonna give that back. - How long have you had this?
- 拜託 米婭 - 很久了
- Come on Mia! - A long time.
你還能在什麼時候看見
When else are you gonna get to see
這麼多好萊塢人員同時聚在一起
a very Hollywood cliche crammed into the same room?
我們會玩的很開心的
We'll make fun of it together!
萊克斯 我對你很失望 這沒什麼好玩的
"I'm disappointed in you, Lex. " There's nothing to make fun of.
這個派對展現出的將會是 最美好的人性
This party is gonna be like... humanity at its finest.
- #手裏握著邀請函 - #默默地記下地址
- #You got the invitation - #You got the right address
#出門之前吃一片藥
#You need some medication?
#希望今天一切順利
#The answer's always "Yes"
#偶然遇到的一個契機
#A little chance encounter
#可能就是盼望已久的機會
#Could be the one you've waited for
#只要多花時間 仔細思索
#Just squeeze a bit more
#今晚我們任務在身 要去試鏡 等待成名
#Tonight we're on a mission Tonight's the casting call
#這次是真正的試鏡
#If this is the real audition
#上帝會保佑我們的
#Oh, God, help us all.
#好好表現 才能名揚四海
#You make the right impression Then everybody knows your name
#我們正在通往夢想的大道上
#We're in the fast lane
#人潮中的過客 也許就是生命中的貴人
#Someone in the crowd could be the one you need to know
#助我放飛夢想
#The one to finally lift you off the ground
#人潮中的過客 也許能展開我新的篇章
#Someone in the crowd could take you where you wanna go
#只要我腳踏實地
#If you're the someone ready to be found
#好好努力
#Someone ready to be found
#只要是你金子 總有一天你會發光
#Do what you need to do 'til they discover you
#讓世人矚目 讓自己信服
#And make you more than who you're seeing now
#當星光匯聚
#So with the stars aligned
#我默默隱退
#I think I'll stay behind
#你要去追尋
#You've got to go and find
人潮中的某人
That someone in the crowd
好樣的
Hey girl!
#人潮中的某人
That someone in the crowd
#你的雙眼 是否僅僅矚目著人潮中的某人
Is someone in the crowd the only thing you really see?
#世界瞬息萬變 你卻巋然不動
Watching while the world keeps spinning 'round?
#總有一個地方
Somewhere there's a place where I find...
#能實現我的夢想
Who I'm gonna be
#總有一個地方
Somewhere...
#等待著我的召喚
That is just waiting to be found
#人潮中的某人 也許就是生命中的貴人
Someone in the crowd could be the one you need to know
#助我放飛夢想
The someone who could lift you off the ground
#人潮中的某人 也許能展開我新的篇章
Someone in the crowd could take you where you want to go
#人潮中的某人
Someone in the crowd could make you
Someone in the crowd could take you
#助我放飛夢想
Flying off the ground
#只要你腳踏實地
If you're someone ready...
#綻放光芒
To be found
不
No.
別這樣 搞什麼
Oh come on! What?
請你別再偷偷摸摸溜進我家了
Please stop sneaking into my home.
你覺得爸媽能管這地方叫家麼
Do you think Mom and Dad would call this a "Home"?
你幹嘛呢
What are you doing?
別這樣 別坐這上面
Please don't do that. Please don't sit on that.
真的麼
Are you kidding?
別坐在這上面
Please don't sit on that.
別在這坐著
Don't sit on that.
- 這是豪吉 卡邁克坐過的凳子 – 我的天啊
- Hoagy Carmichael sat on that. - Oh my god!
- 那個烤西紅柿我已經扔了 – 我真不知道你發什麼神經
- The Baked Potato just threw it away. - I can't imagine why.
- 現在你坐了上去 – 我給你拿了個地毯
- And now you're just sitting on it. - I got you a throw rug.
我不需要
I don't need that.
我要是說 邁爾斯 戴維斯在上面尿尿了呢
What if I said Miles Davis pissed on it?
簡直是侮辱人
It's almost insulting.
不是真的吧
Is it true?
你打算什麼時候收拾這些箱子
When are you going to unpack these boxes?
當我有自己的酒吧的時候
When I unpack them in my own club.
塞巴斯蒂安
Oh, Sebastian!
現在就好像有個女生跟你分手了 你還一直跟蹤人家
It's like a girl broke up with you and you're stalking her.
你沒再回去看了吧
You're not still going by there, are you?
這個
That's...
我不能接受他們把它改造成了個什麼桑巴西班牙參觀
I can't believe they turned it into a samba-tapas place.
- 我的天啊 塞巴斯蒂安 – 又桑巴 又西班牙餅
- Oh my god, Sebastian! - Samba. Tapas.
他們要麼就只選一個 把那一個做好
Pick one, you know. Do one right.
我想讓你見個人
I have someone I want you to meet.
我誰都不想見
I don't want to meet anyone.
不要 我誰都不想見
N- no, I don't want to meet anyone.
- 爸爸給你的嗎 – 是的
- Dad gave you this? - Yes.
你會喜歡她的
You'll like her.
我不覺得我會喜歡她
I don't think I'm gonna like her.
- 她喜歡爵士嗎 – 估計不喜歡
- Does she like jazz? - Probably not.
那我們能聊點什麼
- Then what are we gonna talk about?
我不知道 反正也沒關係
- I dont know! It doesn't matter.
好嗎
Okay?
你生活得跟個隱士一樣
Because you're living like a hermit.
你的車都沒有上保險
You're driving without insurance!
- 有關係嗎 – 是的 有關係
- Doesn't matter? - Yes. Doesn't matter.
- 好吧 – 你得認真一點
- Okay. - You need to get serious.
我還認識一個臉上有紋身的人 你該去見見
Well then I know a guy with a face tattoo you should see.
- 好吧 你真卑鄙 - 我真心的
- Okay, low blow. - With a heart of gold.
- 認真點 – 認真點嗎 勞拉
- Get serious! - Get serious? Laura...
我對我的未來曾經有一個非常認真的計劃
I... I had a very serious plan for my future.
我知道
I know.
這不是我的錯 我被騙了
It's not my fault I got Shanghaied.
你沒被騙 你是被宰了
You didn't get Shanghaied. You got ripped off.
有區別嗎
What's the difference?
我不知道 真相可沒那麼浪漫
I don't know. It's not as romantic as that.
別坐
Don't sit...
所有人都知道那人名聲不好 除了你
Everybody knew that guy was shady, except for you.
你為什麼把浪漫
Why do you say "Romantic"...
說得像髒話似的
like it's a dirty word?
沒付清的賬單可不浪漫 給她打電話
Unpaid bills are not romantic. Call her.
我才不打呢
I'm not going to call her.
事實是 你覺得
The thing is... You're acting like life's...
生活快把我打倒了
got me on the ropes.
但這就是我想要的
I want to be on the ropes.
好嗎 我只是
Okay? I'm just - I'm letting life
讓生活狠狠地打擊我 直到它慫了
hit me until it gets tired.
然後我就反擊 這是經典的以逸待勞
And then I'm gonna hit back. It's a classic "Rope-a-dope".
行了 阿里 我愛你 快收拾你箱子
Okay, Ali. I love you. Unpack your boxes.
- 我會把鎖換了的 – 你換不起
- I'm gonna change the locks. - You can't afford it.
我是涅槃的鳳凰
I am a phoenix rising from the ashes.
- 嗨 - 嗨 比爾 謝謝你讓我回來
- Hey. - Hey Bill, thanks for letting me back.
不客氣
You're welcome.
我想說 我跟以前不一樣了
I want you to know that you're looking at a new man.
好樣的
Good.
- 我現在是一個非常樂意在這裏的人 – 棒極了
- A man that's happy to be here. - Excellent.
- 我現在特別好相處 – 你會按著演出曲目表演對吧
- Very easy to work with. - And you're gonna play the setlist?
非常樂意
Happy to.
雖然沒有人在意我彈什麼
Even though I don't think anybody cares what I play.
但是 好的
But yeah.
如果 沒有人 指的是
Well, if by "Anyone" You mean...
除我之外的人的話 那就對了
anyone other than me, that would be correct.
我在意你彈了什麼 而且我不想聽到自由爵士樂
I care, and I don't wanna hear the free jazz.
行 好的
Right. Okay.
儘管 我
Although I
我以為在這個鎮子上
I thought that in this town worked
是大家互相聽取意見的
on a sort of "One for you, one for me" Type system.
那你意見更重要一點怎麼樣
How about two for you, one for me?
那都聽你的怎麼樣
How about all for you and none for me?
- 棒極了 – 行吧
- That's perfect! Yes. - Great.
-好的 - 好的 共同決定
- Okay. - Okay. Mutual decision.
是的 我決定的
Right. Made made by me.
是的 然後我同意了
Right. And I signed off on it so...
隨便 你怎麼說都好
Whatever. Tell yourself what you wanna know.
歡迎回來
Hello. Welcome back.
這表達方式真好啊 凱倫
There's a nice way to say that, Karen.
塞巴
Seb.
我是聽到你怎麼說了
I do- I do- I hear what you're saying.
但我覺得你說的不是心裏所想的
But I don't think you're saying what you mean.
是嗎 我覺得你沒聽我說的話 你被炒了
Yeah, I don't think you hear what I'm saying. You're fired.
我覺得你嘴上說的
That's what you're saying
不是你心裏想的 你的意思是
but that's not what you mean. You mean is..
滾蛋吧
You're fired.
按演出曲目表演
...play the setlist.
- 不 我說的是 太晚了 - 這是一個警告
- No. What I'm saying is "Too late". - It is a warning.
你到底 你到底來自哪個星球啊
What - what planet are you from?
- 別趕我走 別趕我走 - 很遺憾地通知你 塞巴 你被解雇了
- Don't fire me. Don't fire me. - You're done. I'm sorry, Seb.
可是今天是聖誕節
It's Christmas.
是的 我看到這些裝飾了 祝你新年好運
Yeah, I see the decorations. Good luck in the New Year.
我剛聽到你的演奏了 我想
I just heard you play, and I wanted to...
我不喜歡多軸運動控制器上面那些裂痕
I don't like the fissure on the GT scan.
你做過色盲檢查了嗎
Did you test for achromatopsia?
23日 受害者送達醫院時已死亡 犯罪嫌疑人笑著離開了警察局
D.O.A. On 23rd, perp laughing his face off at the P.D.
該死的米蘭達權利
Damn Miranda Rights.
這是我的課堂
This is my classroom.
要是你不喜歡的話 出門左轉不送
You don't like it, the door is to my left.
女士 你為什麼一直犯那樣的錯誤
Lady why you be tripping like that?
不 賈馬爾
No, Jamal.
你才錯了
You be tripping?
米婭
Mia!
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi! - Hi.
這是我朋友卡洛
I want you to meet my friend Carlo.
- 你好 卡洛 - 我是米婭
- Hi. Carlo. - This is Mia.
- 你叫米婭嗎 - 對 米婭
- Nice. Mia? - Yes, Mia.
- 你好嗎 - 卡洛是個作家
- Hi. How are you? - Carlo is a writer.
是的 人們說我能輕易地
Yeah. They say I have a knack for
就建造出一個虛擬世界 我在這可受歡迎了
world building. I got a lot of heat right now.
人們都在議論我
It's from a lot of buzz,
都在說關於我的事 我真的好興奮
people talking about me. It's just exciting.
你努力工作 然後所有付出都有了回報
You work so hard and then all of it validated...
我去拿杯飲料
I'm gonna go grab a drink.
哦 好的
- Yeah. - Okay.
見到你非常高興
It's really nice to meet you.
不好意思
Sorry.
謝謝 還有要點歌的嗎
Thank you. Any other requests?
前排的這位女生
The girl in the front!
- 逃跑 - 逃跑 這個建議不錯
- 'I Ran'. - 'I Ran'. A fantastic suggestion!
好的 鋼琴手 彈起來 讓我們唱起來
All right, piano man, tickle those ivories. Let's hit it.
一二三四
One two three four!
就是這個感覺
That's right!
#我獨自一人走在這條街上
#I walk alone the avenue
#從未預料可以邂逅如你這般的女孩
#I never thought I'd meet a girl like you
#邂逅如你這般的女孩 我
#Meet a girl like you... - Me?
#棕髮褐眼
#With auburn hair and tawny eyes
#你的那種眼神讓我如此著迷
#The kind of eyes that hypnotize me through
#徹底地使我沉醉其中
#That hypnotize me through
#我開始逃跑 我已經跑了如此之遠
#And I ran, I ran so far away
#然而我始終無法抽身離開
#I couldn't get away
好吧 我想起你了
All right. I remember you.
我承認那天晚上我有些無禮
And I would admit I was a little curt that night.
無禮
"Curt"?
- 好吧 我是個混蛋 我承認 - 對
- Okay, I was an asshole. I can admit that. - Okay.
但是要求一個嚴肅的音樂家
But requesting 'I Ran' from
演奏逃跑這種歌 太過分了
a serious musician is just... it's too far.
天啊 你剛剛是說一個嚴肅的音樂家嗎
My Lord! Did you just say "A serious musician"?
是啊
I don't think so.
- 我能借你的外套嗎 - 為什麼
- Can I borrow what you're wearing? - Why?
因為我下周有個試鏡
Because I have an audition next week.
我將出演一個嚴肅的消防員
I'm playing a serious firefighter.
所以你是個演員
So you're an actress. I thought
你看起來很眼熟 我在哪個節目上見過你嗎
you look familiar. Have I seen you on anything?
華納公司的咖啡店裏 經典一幕
A coffee shop on the Warner Bros. Lot. That's classic.
- 噢 我想起來了 - 對
- Oh, I see. - Yeah.
你是個咖啡師
You're a barista.
現在我知道
And I can see how you could
原來您居於如此高位 怪不得看不起我
then look down on me from all the way up there.
下一首
Next set.
他不 我不
He doesn't... I don't...
他從不告訴我要幹什麼
He doesn't tell me what to do.
- 他剛剛才告訴你 - 我知道 我讓他告訴我的
- He just told you what to... - I know. I let him.
- 你叫什麼名字 - 米婭 - 米婭
- What is your name? - Mia. - Mia.
我猜某天會在電影裏看到你
I guess I'll see you in the movies.
- 你知道約瑟夫 坎貝爾嗎 - 知道
- You know Joseph Campbell? - Yes.
我有這麼一個想法
I have this idea that you were
你可以從熊的角度
reimagining "Goldilocks and the Three Bears"...
來重新塑造金鳳花姑娘和三隻熊這個故事
from the perspective of the bears.
- 這會很驚悚吧 - 說不定還可以得到什麼特權
- You know it's thrilling. - It could be a franchise.
是的
Right.
我們不知道
So well we don't know if
他們有沒有被關在上面 我們不知道
they were cooped up up there. We don't know.
喬治 邁克爾
George Michael!
你好
Hello.
不好意思 我認識那個人
Sorry. It's - I know that guy.
你拿了你車鑰匙了嗎
Did you get your keys?
- 拿了 - 你能幫忙取一下我的嗎
- Yes. - Can you grab mine?
什麼
Sorry what?
你能幫忙取一下 我的鑰匙嗎
Will you be able to grab my... my keys?
我聽不清
I can't hear you.
- 不好意思 你能取一下我鑰匙嗎 - 噢
- Sorry, can you grab my keys? - Oh.
- 拜託 - 好的吧
- Please. - Oh, there we go.
- 謝謝 - 不用謝
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
- 哪種車 - 普銳斯
- What kind? - It's a Prius.
- 有好多普銳斯 - 有綠帶子的那個
- That does't help me. - With a green ribbon.
好了
All right.
鞋子看起來 額 很舒服
Those look, uh, comfortable.
是的
They are.
謝謝你讓我脫離了這無聊的派對
Thank you for saving the day back there.
你其實沒有給我太多選擇
Well, you didn't really give me much of a choice.
很奇怪我們一直遇見對方
It's pretty strange that we keep running into each other.
是有點奇怪
It is strange.
或許這意味著些什麼
Maybe it means something.
- 是嗎 - 是啊 或許是的
- I doubt it. - Yeah. I don't think so.
我車呢
Where's my car?!
把那個放在你下巴那
Put that thing to your chin.
- 這個 - 是的
- This? - Yeah.
它把你的頭變成了個天線
It makes your head into an antenna.
這會使你患上癌癥 但你能快點找到你的車
I think it gives you cancer but you find your car faster.
什麼
What?
我是說你活得不會太久
I mean you don't get to live as long but you get
但這樣你就會更快到達目的地 所以影響就相互抵消了
where you're going quicker so it all evens out.
- 這話太難聽了 - 只是一個建議
- That sounds terrible. - Just a suggestion.
你真是一個
You're a real...
- 我想說什麼來著 - 身穿閃亮盔甲的騎士
- What's the word am I looking for? - Knight in shining armor.
- 怪人 想說的就是這個 - 好吧
- Weirdo. That was the word. - Okay.
沒什麼可看的 是吧
Not much to look at, huh?
我見過更美的地方
I've seen better.
#暮色西沉
#The sun is nearly gone
#華燈未上
#The lights are turning on
#海天相接處銀光閃閃
#A silver shine that stretches to the sea
#我們在這般景色下偶遇
#We stumbled on a view.
#像是上天的精心安排
#That's tailor made for two
#但結果卻讓人難過
#What a shame
#無論對你 還是我
#to our, you and me
#換做別的俊男靚女
#Some other girl and guy
#肯定會享受這片別緻的天空
#Would love this swirling sky
#但現在卻只有你我兩人
#But there's only you and I
#彼此沒有那種心動的感覺
#And we've got no shot
#沒有一見鍾情
#This could never be
- #你也不是我中意的類型 - 是嗎
- #You're not the type for me - Really?
#此情此景 卻沒有半點火花
#And there's not a spark in sight
#如此良辰 真煞風景
#What a waste of a lovely night
#你說對我沒感覺
#You say there's nothing here?
#好 我先把話說清楚
#Well, let's make something clear
#要說也是我先說
#I think I'll be the one to make that call
#你要說什麼
#What's you call?
#儘管你英俊又瀟灑
#And though you look so cute
- #西裝革履 - 這是羊毛的
- #in your polyester suit - It's wool.
#但你說得對 我才不會愛上你
#You're right, I'd never fall for you at all
#也許你能迷倒
#And maybe this appeals
#那些不諳世事的女孩
#To someone not in heels
#或是那些
#Or to any girl who feels
#對你情迷意亂的女孩
#there's some chance for romance
- #但說真的 我對你沒有多少感覺 - #一點都沒有嗎
- #But I'm frankly feeling nothing - #Is that so?
#甚至一點點都沒有
#Or it could be less than nothing
#這麼說你也同意咯
#Good to know so you agree?
#沒錯
#That's right
#如此良辰 真煞風景
#What a waste of a lovely night
嗨 格雷格
Hi, Greg.
抱歉 我遲到了
Hi. Oh, sorry I'm late.
好 馬上到 好的 拜
Yeah. Very soon. Okay. Bye.
- 車就在這 - 就在這
- It's just right there. - Just right here.
要我載你去找車麼
Do you want a ride to your car?
不用 我的車就在旁邊
No, I'm just right up here.
晚安
Good night.
打擾一下 這是無谷蛋白的 是吧
Excuse me. This is gluten free, right?
- 不是 - 什麼
- No - What?
我要退掉
I'd like a refund.
好的 我去看一下
Okay. Let me check it out.
米婭 週五你不上班
Mia, you're closing Friday.
週五我得上班 我有個試鏡 還記得嗎
I can't close on Friday. I have an audition, remember?
你覺得我在意你的試鏡嗎 我們說好了的
Do I look like I care? We schedule it.
還有 明天我們要開個小會
Oh and we need to have a little talk tomorrow, okay?
- 把你圍裙弄弄好 - 好的
- Fix your apron, please. - Okay.
又是你
You again!
你在這裏幹什麼
What are you doing here?
就是開個會啊 見個工作室老大啊什麼的
You know, just meetings and studio heads..
你是怎麼進片場的
How did you get on the lot?
我基本上是從安檢門衝進來的
I basically just run past the guard gates.
我覺得還要二十分鐘 他們才能發現我
I think I have 20 minutes until they find me.
- 一會兒你就休息了 是吧 - 我十分鐘後下班
- You have a break coming up, do you? - I'm off in ten minutes.
我能去洗手間躲躲嗎
Can I hide in the bathroom?
- 好的 - 好的
- Yes. - Okay.
抱歉
Sorry.
我還是要去看一下 抱歉
I actually do have to check. I'm sorry.
亨弗萊 鮑嘉和英格麗 褒曼在卡薩布蘭卡裏
That's the window that Humphrey Bogart
就是通過這扇窗戶向下看的
and Ingrid Bergman looked out of in Casablanca.
- 哇哦 - 是吧
- Wow. - Yeah.
真不敢相信你就在這對面上班
I can't believe you work right across the street from there.
- 是吧 - 太神奇了
- Yeah. - That's amazing.
你的 白馬王子 叫什麼來著
What was you're, uh, you're Bogart's name?
他叫什麼名字 是格雷格嗎
What's his name? Is it Greg?
是的 格雷格
Yeah, Greg.
好吧 你們交往多久了
Right. How long have you been...?
我們在一起大約一個月了
We've been seeing each other for about a month.
不錯啊
That's great.
他呀 他人很好 反正 我喜歡住在這附近
He's... uh... He's sweet. Anyway, I love being around this stuff.
你懂嗎
You know?
我知道你的意思 我到五英里外的地方買咖啡
I know what you mean. I get coffee 5 miles out of the way...
- 就是為了能靠近一家爵士樂俱樂部 - 真的嗎
- just so I can be near a jazz club. - Really?
是啊 貝克先鋒俱樂部 知道這家嗎
Yeah, the Van Beek. Do you know it?
大牌的搖擺樂團都在那裏演出過
All the big swing bands used to play there.
考特 貝茜 奇克 韋伯
Count Basie, Chick Webb.
不過 現在它現在變成了桑巴西班牙餐館
Anyway, it's a samba-tapas place now...
所以
So...
桑巴西班牙餐館是什麼
What's a samba-tapas place?
就是一個賣西班牙餅的桑巴舞廳
You know, it's like a samba place where they serve tapas.
- 哦 - 是啊 時間是把 殺豬刀
- Oh. - Yeah. So the joke's on... history?
我也說不好 這就是洛杉磯
I dont know. That's L.A.
他們
They just
他們追求一切 又不懂珍惜
They worship everything and they value nothing.
我們要開拍了 請止步
We're about to roll. Stop please guys.
- 你們要開拍了 - 是啊
- You're rolling? - Yeah.
他們天天在我家邊上拍電影 我們不會礙事的
They shoot movies on my street all the time so no problem.
- 來這邊 - 好的
- Come this way. - Right.
要清場
It's a lockdown.
- 我喜歡她 - 準備開始
- I love her! - And here we go.
米婭 你是怎麼進來的
Hey, Mia. How did you get into this?
- 準備 拍攝 - 進哪啊
- And... roll! - Get into what?
- 就是 電影啊 表演啊 - 開拍
- You know, movies, acting. - Action!
- 我姑媽是一名演員 - 哦 這樣
- My aunt was an actress. - Oh, okay.
她在旅行劇團工作
She was in a traveling theatre company.
我在內華達州的博爾德市長大
I grew up in Boulder City, Nevada.
我家對面
So across the street from my house,
有一家小圖書館
there was this little library..
裏面有一個老電影區
that had an old movies section.
所以她 她帶我去那裏
So she - she took me and spent an entire day
一整天都在看那些老電影
watching all these old movies...
像是 美人計 育嬰奇譚 卡薩布蘭卡 還有
like "Notorious", "Bringing Up Baby," "Casablanca" And...
這裏停一下 卡 看一下錄像帶
Cut it there! Cut! Check the tapes.
- 我們現在能說話了 - 聽起來她很了不起
- We can talk now. - She sounds incredible.
她是真的很了不起 我會
She was incredible. And I
把所有的劇本放在我的臥室
would put on all these plays in my bedroom...
然後基本上就是我和她
and it would basically just she and I...
重現電影裏的橋段
reenacting the scenes from the movies.
- 然後我寫了一部自己劇本 - 哇哦 - 是的
- And then I wrote my own plays. - Wow. - Yeah
我喜歡這裏
I love it.
總而言之 大學畢業兩年後我來到了這裏
So anyway, I left college after two years to come here.
還有 我上一次的試鏡是一個青少年肥皂劇
And my last audition was for a teen soap...
是把 危險遊戲 和 橘子郡男孩 糅在一起的類型
pitched as Dangerous Minds meets The OC.
所以說 唉 當初該去做律師的
So yeah, should've been a lawyer.
因為這個社會需要更多的律師
'Cause the world needs more lawyers.
不需要更多的女演員
Doesn't need more actresses.
你不止是個演員
You're not just an actress.
不止是個演員 是什麼意思
What do you mean "Just an actress"?
你自己也說了 你是個劇作家神童
You said it yourself. You were a child prodigy playwright.
我可沒這麼說
That is not what I said.
你只是太謙虛了 但事實確實如此
Well, you're too modest to say it but it's true.
所以你完全可以為你自己寫劇本嘛 比如
So you could just write your own roles, you know.
寫些和你一樣有趣的角色
Write something that's as interesting as you are...
你根本就沒必要去試鏡嘛
and you don't have to audition for this pishi kaka.
是哈
Yeah.
你看路易斯 阿姆斯特郎
Look at Louis Armstrong, you know.
他本可以只演奏
He could have just played
那些別人給他的行進曲的樂譜
the marching band charts that he was given.
- 但是他沒有那麼做 他做了什麼呢 - 他做了什麼
- But he didn't do it. What did he do? - What did he do?
他創造了歷史 不是嗎
He made history, didn't he?
你是說要我不要去試鏡了
Well, I'm gonna stop
而是應該去創造歷史
auditioning and I'm gonna make history instead.
嗯哼 我只能幫你到這了
Well, my work is done here.
我想是時候跟你坦白了
I should probably tell you something now.
說實話
To get it out the way.
我討厭爵士樂
I hate jazz.
你還好嗎
You okay?
你說你討厭爵士樂是什麼意思
What do you mean you hate jazz?
就是我聽爵士樂的時候 不覺得喜歡的意思啊
It just means that when I listen to it, I don't like it.
嗯 但這只是你不喜歡爵士樂的籠統說法罷了
Yeah but it's just a blanket statement that you don't like jazz.
你接下來有事嗎
What are you doing right now?
沒事
Nothing.
我在想啊 當人們在說
You know, I just think that when people say that,
你知道的 討厭爵士樂時
you know, hate jazz..
他們只是不懂而已
They just don't have context.
不知道它從何而來
They don't know where it comes from.
知道嗎
You know?
爵士樂誕生於新奧爾良的一小間低級住所
Jazz was born in a little flophouse in New Orleans...
就因為那裏擠滿了各地的人
and just because people were crammed in there,
說著五種不同的語言
they spoke five different languages.
他們沒法交流
They couldn't talk to each other.
他們能交流的唯一媒介便是爵士樂
The only way that they could communicate was with jazz.
那肯尼 基呢
You know, what about Kenny G?
什麼
What?
肯尼 基呢 我是說電梯裏的輕音樂呢
What about Kenny G? I mean, what about elevator music?
也就是我所瞭解的爵士樂
You know, jazz music that I know.
- 電梯音樂怎麼了 - 我生活中接觸到的
- What about it? - From my life.
我只是 我想說它讓人感到放鬆
I just - I mean find it relaxing.
它並不放鬆 並不是
It's not relaxing. It's not.
並不是
It's not!
西德尼 貝謝打了人
Sidney Bechet shot somebody...
就是因為那人說他吹錯了個音
because he told him he played a wrong note.
這可不叫放鬆
That's hardly relaxing.
我成長的地方 有個叫KJAZZ 103的電台
Where I grew up, there was this station called KJAZZ 103.
當人們開雞尾酒會的時候
And people would just put on
就會播放那個電台
that station when they had a cocktail party...
然後呢
Right.
接著每個人就只是聊天 並沒人聽
And everyone would just kind of talk over it.
- 我懂 - 對啊 這就
- I know. - Yes. It was..
對 我懂 所以我就覺得那 那是
Okay, okay. So I think that that's...
一部分問題就是你聽不到它 這樣
part of the problem is that you can't hear it, you know.
你就得去看 得去發現一些已經岌岌可危的東西
You have to see it, you have to see what's at stake.
我是說 看看這些人 看看那個正在吹薩克斯的人
I mean, look at these fellas. Look at the saxophonist right now.
他完全掌控了這首曲子 其中有他自己的成分
He just hijacked the song. He's on his own trail.
這些人都在作曲
Everyone of these guys are composing,
在自我編排 他們這是在創作
rearranging, they're writing...
在演奏旋律 他們就是
and they're playing the melody. They're just...
現在你看 那個小號手 他有自己的思路
And now look, the trumpet player. He's got his own idea.
這是衝突與融合的過程 這就是
It's conflict and it's compromise, and it's just...
每一次都是新的 每晚都是完全不同的
It's new every time. It's brand new every night.
非常 非常地激動人心
It's very, very exciting.
然而它卻瀕臨滅亡
And it's dying.
它在滅亡啊 米婭 它正在一點一滴地消亡
It's dying, Mia. It's dying on the vine.
人們卻說 讓它去吧 它已經過了它的黃金時段
And the world says, "Let it die. It had its time".
但在我眼皮底下休想
Well, not on my watch.
那你打算怎麼辦
What are you gonna do?
我會創建我自己的俱樂部
I'll have my own club.
- 真的嗎 - 真的
- Really? - Yes.
那樣我們想演奏什麼就演奏什麼 想什麼時候演奏就什麼時候演奏
We're gonna play whatever we want, whenever we want...
想怎樣演奏就怎樣演奏 只要是純粹的爵士樂
however we want, as long as it's pure jazz.
你好 我是米婭 多蘭
Hi, this is Mia Dolan.
是的 剛剛沒接到
Yeah, I just missed a call.
- 給我回復啦 - 什麼
- I got a callback! - What?
快說 是什麼
Come on! For what?
一部電視劇 我剛跟你說的那部
For a TV show. The one I was telling you about.
- 危險遊戲 遇上 橘子郡男孩 - 對
- The Dangerous Minds meets The OC? - Yeah.
- 恭喜你啊 簡直難以置信 - 真的好開心
- Congratulations! That's incredible! - It's really exciting.
我之前好像還說它壞話來著
I feel like I said negative stuff about if before.
說什麼了
What?
像 莫名其妙的叛逆 之類的
It's like "Rebel Without a Cause" Sort of.
我可是有子彈的人 這樣嗎
"I got the bullets!"
對的
Yes.
- 你沒看過吧 - 沒看過
- You've never seen it! - I've never seen it.
天哪 你知不知道麗都街都在放這個
Oh my. You know it's playing in the Rialto.
- 真的嗎 - 對啊
- Really? - Yes.
你應該去看看 我是說 我 我可以帶你去看
You should go. I mean, I - I can take you.
- 好啊 - 你懂的 去給你普及一下
- Okay. - You know, for research.
- 普及一下 好啊 - 對
- For research. Yeah. - Yeah.
好的
Okay.
週一晚 十點
Monday night, ten o'clock.
- 好的 很棒 - 好
- Yeah. Great. - Okay.
為了普及哈
For research.
#星光之城啊 你是否只為我閃耀
#City of stars are you shining just for me?
#星光之城啊 世間有太多不可明瞭
#City of stars there's so much that I can't see
#誰又能明瞭
#Who knows?
#這究竟是一切美好開始的預兆
#Is this the start of something wonderful and new?
#還是又是黃粱一夢呢
#Or one more dream that I cannot make true?
- 請站在那 - 好的 很高興見到你
- Stand there please. - Okay. Nice to meet you.
- 你好 - 你好
- Hi. - Hi.
- 可以開始了 - 好的
- On your own time. - Okay.
給你兩個選擇
Two options:
聽我的 或者是聽我的 明白了嗎
You either follow my rules, or follow my rules. Capisce?
謝謝你
Thank you.
- 謝謝 - 我可以換種演法
- Thanks. - I could do it a different way.
不用了 非常感謝你的表演 感謝
That's fine. Thank you very much. Thank you.
- 很開心 謝謝你 - 再見
- That was fun. Thanks. - Bye.
嘿 米婭
Hey Mia.
- 怎麼啦 - 格雷格來了
- What? - Greg's here.
怎麼回事
What do you mean...?
嘿 寶貝 訂到前排位置了
Hey babe. Got a space out front.
- 太棒啦 - 我們得出發了
- Great! - We should get going.
我哥哥的飛機提前著陸了
My brother landed really early.
你忘了嗎
Did you forget?
- 該死的 - 你忘了
- Shit. - You forgot.
是今晚啊
That's tonight.
- 沒關係 - 好吧 - 你忘了 - 啊 好吧
- That's okay. - Yeah. - You forgot. - Yeah. Okay. All right.
那我就換衣服
So then I'll just get changed.
- 好勒 - 好 - 真棒 - 棒
- Okay. - Okay. - Great. - Great.
嗯 是他打電話來了 嗨 喬西 對
Yeah, that's him. Hey, Josh. Yeah.
就接一下米婭 到那大概
Just picking up Mia. We'll be there in like...
但是現在我們有了立體音響
But now we got this surround sound setup.
噢 就像是在電影院一樣
Oh, it's like being in a movie theater.
嗯 好過電影院音效 真的
Well, better than being in a theater, really.
- 真是拭目以待 - 你知道現在的劇院
- I can't wait. - You know theaters these days.
- 是的 - 環境很糟糕
- Yeah. - They're so dirty.
是的 我知道 烏煙瘴氣的
Yeah, I know. They smell bad.
- 要麼太熱要麼就太冷
- And they're either too hot or too cold.
- 我明白 音質真是一落千丈
- I know, the quality has gone far and off.
噢 真的很糟糕 總有人在說話
Oh, it's terrible and there's always people talking.
- 很多人 - 噢 這
- Many people. - Oh it's...
- 抱歉  - 稍等一下
- I'm sorry. Just - hold on a second.
- 你好  - 可能是工作
- Hello? - It's probably work.
抱歉 所以你知道 我們很喜歡
Sorry. So you know, we love it.
- 很好 - 你們一定得來
- It's so nice. - Well you have to come.
你真應該過來
You should come by.
我還有一個地方要介紹給你 印度尼西亞
I have one more for you man: Indonesia.
我不知道 我從沒聽別人說過
I don't know. I never heard anyone say that.
我知道 你知道我都記不清了
I know, you know I can't even keep
但是老實說 那真是改變了我的人生
track of it but honestly, it was just life changing.
- 真的 - 是的
- Really. - Yeah.
很奇妙
Is it amazing?
- 是的 - 一個五星級叢林生態度假勝地
- Yes. - A five-star jungle-eco resort.
- 你可能不相信 - 棒極了
- Well, you would not believe. - Amazing.
我們本來打算去尼加拉瓜
We were thinking about going to Nicaragua.
我覺得尼加拉瓜還不夠發達
I think Nicaragua is less developed.
- 甚至有點落後 - 是的
- It's a bit underdeveloped. - Right.
是有一點
It's a little more.
我只是 我不知道 我不知道那裏是否安全
I just- I don't know- I don't know if it's safe there.
- 是的 是的  - 我不知道是否安全
- Yeah. Yeah. - I don't know if it's safe.
對不起
I'm sorry!
我有個主意
I have an idea.
那是什麼 劇本嗎
What is that? Is that a script?
- 是一個戲劇 - 一個戲劇
- It's a play. - A play?
你最好給我們所有角色
You better give us all roles!
事實上 是一個女人的獨角戲
Actually, it's a one woman show.
所以我不能
So I can't.
哇 每次都要這樣嗎
Wow. Is that gonna happen everytime?
我覺得是
I think so.
等一下 這是單行道
Wait! It's one way.
塞巴斯蒂安
Sebastian!
- 凱斯 - 過來 夥計
- Keith. - Come here, man.
- 最近怎麼樣 - 很好 夥計
- How are you? - Very good, man.
這是米婭 米婭 這是凱斯
This is Mia. Mia, Keith.
- 嗨 米婭 很高興見到你 - 很高興見到你
- Hi Mia. Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
我以前經常和這個傢伙一起演奏
I used to play with this guy.
我們以前一起上學
We went to school together.
- 你近來怎麼樣 兄弟 - 很好
- So how you been brother? - Great.
從來都沒這麼好 你呢
Never been better. How about you?
我也非常好 一直很忙
I've been really good. Been very busy.
- 我組建了一個小型樂團 - 很好
- I got a new combo. - Okay.
不錯
Cool.
我們在找鍵盤手
We're looking for keys.
- 你開玩笑吧 - 不 我是認真的
- Are you kidding me? - No, I'm not kidding.
- 算了 我不去了 - 你確定 是付費的哦
- No, I'm good. - You sure? It pays.
我不去了
I'm good.
我去拿點喝的
Let's just grab a drink then.
真是太長時間不見了
It's been too long.
- 好的 很高興見到你米婭 - 很高興見到你
- Okay. Nice to meet you Mia. - Nice to meet you.
劇終
The end.
這
It's...
太有才了
Genius!
- 真的嗎 - 是的
- Really? - Yes.
我感覺這劇真的很懷舊
It feels really nostalgic to me.
- 這就是重點 - 是不是太懷舊了
- That's the point. - Is it too nostalgic?
- 那是 - 觀眾會喜歡嗎
- That's... - Are people gonna like it?
去他的觀眾
Fuck 'em!
- 你總是這麼說 - 我真的相信
- You always say that. - Well, I truly believe that.
- 我給你做了個東西 - 幹什麼用的
- I made you something. - For what?
給你的俱樂部
For your club.
為什麼叫seb『s
Why does it say "Seb's"?
因為我覺得應該叫seb『s
Cause I think you should call it "Seb's".
什麼
What?
因為沒人會願意去雞肉串俱樂部
'Cause no one's gonna come to "Chicken on a Stick".
- 這是音符嗎 是單引號嗎 - 是的
- Is that a music note? Is it an apostrophe? - Yes.
真的很酷 應該叫做雞肉串
That's pretty cool. It's gotta be "Chicken on a Stick".
因為查利 帕克就有個外號
Because Charlie Parker got his nickname...
我知道 因為他喜歡雞肉
I know because he loves chicken.
這就是為什麼他們叫他大鳥
That's why they call him "Bird".
所以我要有雞肉 啤酒 爵士 雞肉串
So I'm gonna have chicken, beer, jazz. "Chicken on a Stick"
我知道 我覺得你應該放棄雞肉
I know. I think you should drop the chicken,
只要酒水和爵士樂 還有
and just have drinks and jazz, and...
- 還可以有  - 我不想放棄雞肉的
- also there could be... - I'm not dropping the chicken.
你也許可以在其他地方做
You could maybe do it somewhere else.
比如找一個新地方
Find a new spot?
- 必須是貝克先鋒俱樂部
- It's gotta be the Van Beek.
- 不一定非得是貝克先鋒
- It doesn't have to be the Van Beek.
我不能讓他們在原來的爵士聖地上盡情的跳桑巴
I can't let them samba all over its history.
我不能這麼做
I can't do it.
- 他們可以跳的 只是你自己不想讓他們跳罷了 - 你戲劇寫得真好
- You can let them but you refuse to. - Your play's incredible.
你知道嗎 整個世界都在你的臥室
You know? The whole world from your bedroom.
他們還想要什麼 有誰這麼做了
What else do they want? Who's doing that?
- 我 - 對就是你
- I'm doing that. - You're doing that.
燈塔酒吧裏的傢伙是誰
Who was that guy in The Lighthouse?
- 給你演出機會的那個人 - 凱斯
- The guy that offered you the gig? - Keith.
是的 你們倆為什麼那麼彆扭呢
Yeah. Why was it so weird between you two?
我跟在一起他一直都這麼彆扭
It's - it's just always weird with him.
真的嗎 - 是的
- Really? - Yeah.
但是他看起來人還不錯 還給你提供工作
But he seemed kinda nice because he did offer you a job.
你會給他打電話嗎
Are you gonna call him?
- 不 不 - 好吧
- No. No. - All right.
所以
So...
- 我們達成共識 - 嗯
- Here's what we know. - Yeah.
一定得叫 雞肉串
It's definitely "Chicken on a Stick"...
你的表演一定會成功的
and your play's gonna be a triumph.
是一個女人的獨角戲
It's a one woman show.
所以只有我一個
So it's just me.
不 我的意思是我會出演
No, I mean I'm acting in it.
不是 媽媽 沒有報酬 我要出錢來做
No, Mom, I'm not getting paid. I'm paying to do it.
他很好 他準備開自己的爵士俱樂部
He's great. He's gonna open his own jazz club.
是的 一定會很棒
Yeah, it's gonna be incredible.
呃 不 他 他還沒成名 他需要
Uh no. He's - he's nobody yet. He needs um..
他在存錢 我覺得
He's saving up, I think.
不 他還沒有固定的演出
No but he doesn't have a steady gig.
但是他會搞定的
But he's figuring it out.
最近有點亂
It's just been a little too gilly lately.
媽媽 他會想辦法把俱樂部開起來的 你一定會喜歡的
Mom, he's gonna find a way to open it and you're gonna love it.
好嗎
Okay?
爸爸怎麼樣了
How's Dad?
塞巴斯蒂安 進來 夥計
Sebastian. Come on in, man.
- 感謝你能來 - 謝謝你邀請我
- Thanks for coming. - Thanks for having me.
沒想到今天能見到你
I wasn't sure I'd see you today.
計劃是這樣的 好
- So here's the deal. - Okay.
我們和環球有發行合作 會有自己的專輯
We got distribution with Universal. We got our own imprint.
也會有路演
We're about to go on the road.
我們會付你周薪一千美金
We can pay you a thousand bucks a week...
加上門票和專輯銷售分紅 聽起來怎麼樣
plus a cut of the ticket revenue and merchandising. Sound good?
- 塞巴斯蒂安 - 嗯
- Sebastian? - Yup.
可以嗎
All right.
那我們開始吧 好的
- Let's play. - Okay.
我知道 這風格迥異
I know. It's different.
你說你想拯救爵士
But you say you want to save jazz.
如果沒人聽爵士你拿什麼來拯救它
How are you gonna save jazz if no one's listening?
就是因為像你這樣的人才導致爵士樂的衰亡
Jazz is dying because of people like you.
你演奏的是燈塔酒吧裏那種老式90年代的腔調
You play into 90 year olds at The Lighthouse.
小孩子們呢 年輕人呢
Where are the kids? Where are the young people?
你對肯尼克 拉克和塞隆尼斯 蒙克如此著迷
You're so obsessed with Kenny Clarke and Thelonious Monk.
這些人都是革命者
These guys were revolutionaries.
如果你自己就是個保守派
How are you going to be a revolutionary,
你要怎麼成為革命者
if you're such a traditionalist?
你過於執著於往昔 而爵士是關於未來
You holding on to the past, but jazz is about the future.
我懂你 我還認識一個鍵盤手 他沒你優秀
I know. The other guy, he wasn't as good as you.
但你太糾結了 兄弟
But you're a pain in the ass, man.
#繁星之城 你是否唯我一人閃耀
#City of stars Are you shining just for me?
#繁星之城 如此之多迷亂我的眼眸
#City of stars There's so much that I can't see
#又有何人知曉
#Who knows?
#從我第一次與你相擁 就已感知這美好
#I felt it from the first embrace I shared with you
#如今我們美夢成真
#That now our dreams they've finally come true
#繁星之城
#City of stars
#無數人所追逐的就是
#Just one thing everybody wants
#在燈紅酒綠之中
#There in the bars
#穿過擁擠餐廳
#And through the smokescreen
#透過繚繞煙幕
#Of the crowded restaurants
#這就是愛
#It's love
#是啊 每個人都在尋求他人的愛意
#Yes, all we're looking for is love from someone else
- #一次衝動 - #一個眼神
- #A rush - #A glance
- #一次觸碰 - #一曲舞蹈
- #A touch - #A dance
#一個眼神明了心意
#A look in somebody's eyes
#點亮星空
#To light up the skies
#展開世界的畫捲滾動在你眼前
#To open the world and send it reeling
#一個聲音說道 你我相會再此
#A voice that says, "I'll be here and you'll be alright
#我不在意我將會去往何方
#I don't care if I know just where I will go
#因為此刻我只需擁有這美妙的感覺
#'Cause all that I need's this crazy feeling
#蠢蠢欲動的心
#The rat-tat-tat on my heart
#我只希望此刻永駐
#I think I want it to stay
#繁星之城 你是否為我一人閃耀
#City of stars Are you shining just for me?
#繁星之城
#City of stars
#你從未如此閃耀
#You never shined so brightly
#我不知道為何舞動身姿
#I don't know why I keep moving my body
#我不知曉對錯與否
#I don't know if this is wrong or if it's right
#我不知道是否是節奏或許只是瘋魔
#I don』t know if there`s a beat, or somethinga`s taking over me
#我所知
#And I just know...
#這感覺如此美好
#I'll feel so good tonight
#我不知曉卻喜歡你的姓名
#I don't know what your name is but I like it
#佔據思緒的是
#I've been thinking about some things
#我想嘗試的事情
#I wanna try
#不知你為何到來 但我瞭解我心中所想
#I don't know what you came to do, but I wanna do it with you
#我所知
#And I just know...
#這感覺如此美好
#I'll feel so good tonight
#啊 如果我們繼續跳舞
#Oh, if we keep on dancing
#隨著我們的節奏到高潮
#Take our rhythm to new heights
#感受著激情的火熱 點燃著夜晚
#Feel the heat of passion, baby Light up the night
#我們可以點亮全場
#We could start a fire
#來吧 寶貝 讓我們沉浸其中
#Come on, let it burn baby
#我們可以點亮全場
#We could start a fire
#讓我們坦誠相待 寶貝
#Let the tables turn baby
#我們可以點亮全場
#We could start a fire
#我僅知這感覺如此美好
#I just know I feel so good
#你知道嗎 這感覺如此美好
#Don't you know I feel so good
情緒正酣 氣氛正濃
a??I just know I feel so good
#今夜
#Tonight
#我不在意
#I don't care...
#是否變成一場狂歡
#If this turns into a riot
#讓我們撒野 嗨翻全場
#Lets get reckless, tear this place down to the floor
#音樂調到最高
#Turn the music way up loud
#沒有人可以阻擋
#Can't nobody stop us now
#這感覺如此美好
#I just know I feel so good...
#今夜
#Tonight
#這感覺如此美好
#I just know I feel so good...
#今夜
#Tonight
#我們可以點燃全場
#We could start a fire
#來吧 寶貝 讓我們沉浸其中
#Come on, let it burn baby
#我們可以點燃全場
#We could start a fire
#讓我們坦誠相待 寶貝
#Let the tables turn baby
我們可以點燃全場
a??We could start a fire
#這感覺如此美好
#I just know I feel so good
#你可知這感覺如此美好
#Don't you know I feel so good
#你可知道
#Don't you know, dona€?t you know?
#今夜
#Tonight
嗨 是我
Hey, it's me.
我不確定你現在在哪裏 可能在波士頓
I'm not sure where you are right now. I think Boston.
也可能是達拉斯 我不確定
Maybe Dallas, I don't know.
最近都沒怎麼聯繫了
I haven't heard from you in a little while...
我很想你
And I miss you.
就這樣 拜
All right bye.
我以為
I thought...
驚喜
Surprise!
我明天要一大早離開 但我就是
I gotta leave first thing in the morning, but I just...
想見到你
I had to see you.
回家了真高興
It's so nice to be home.
我也很高興你回來
I'm so glad you're home.
演出怎麼樣
How's the play going?
我很緊張
I'm nervous.
怎麼會 為什麼
You are? Why?
- 因為 如果觀眾真的來現場  - 不要管他
- Because... what if people show up? - Pishi kaka.
你真的那麼在意觀眾的看法嗎
You're nervous about what they think?
我真的很緊張
I'm nervous to do it.
很緊張站在台上
I'm nervous to get up on that stage...
為觀眾演出
and perform for people.
我是說這些都不必要
I mean, I don't need to say that to you.
這場演出肯定驚艷四座 你不懂我很怕
- It's gonna be incredible. - You don't get it but I'm terrified.
能觀賞演出是他們的榮幸 我迫不及待了
They should be lucky to see it. I can't wait.
可我想等
I can.
你明天什麼時候離開 早上嗎
When do you leave? In the morning?
45分走 去博伊西（美國愛達荷州首府）
45. Boise.
- 要去博伊西 - 是的
- Boise? - Boise.
敬博伊西
To Boise!
你也應該來
You should come.
去博伊西
To Boise?
這樣就完成了你又一項心願清單
Yeah. You can knock it off your bucket list.
哦 那相當不錯嘛 我也想去啊
Oh. That would be really exciting. I wish I could.
那之後你準備去哪兒
What are you doing after the tour?
你為什麼不來
Why can't you?
- 去博伊西 - 沒錯
- Come to Boise? - Yeah.
因為我還要排練
'Cause I have to rehearse.
難道不可以去其他地方排練嗎
Yeah but can't you rehearse anywhere?
其他你在的地方
Anywhere you are?
我是說 - 沒錯
I mean - I guess.
好吧 我的道具什麼的都在這裏 而且只有兩星期了
Well, all my stuff is here and it's in two weeks.
所以我覺得這可能不是個
So I don't think really think that would be...
好吧
Okay.
- 最好的決定 不過 - 好吧
- the best idea right now, but... - Right.
我希望我能去
I wish I could.
現在我們必須努力然後見到對方
We're just gonna have to try and see each other,
你知道的 才能見到對方
you know, so that we see each other.
我知道 不過你什麼時候結束這個
I know but when are you done?
你什麼意思 我是說
What do you mean? I mean...
什麼時候結束巡迴演出
When you're finish with the whole tour?
結束以後 我們會去錄音
After we finish, we're gonna go to recording
接著我們再去巡迴演出
and then we'll go back on tour.
你知道的 我們巡迴演出才能接著出唱片
You know, we tour so we can make the records...
然後我們再去巡迴演出再出唱片
so we can go back to tour the record.
所以這就像持久戰
So it's like the long haul?
你說 持久戰 什麼意思
What do you mean the "Long haul"?
我說持久戰的意思是你得待在這個樂隊裏
I mean the long haul that you're gonna stay in this band...
一直巡迴演出
for a long time.
就像一場持久戰
On tour.
那你本以為我要做什麼
I mean, what did you think I was going to do?
我不
I don't...
我沒想過這件事
I hadn't really thought it through.
我不知道你們樂隊
I didn't know that the band...
- 你沒想過我們會火起來 - 有那麼重要
- You didn't think we would be successful. - would be important.
不 我不是那麼認為的 我只是覺得你
No, that's not really what I mean. I just mean that y-you...
我是說 你會巡迴演出多久 幾個月 幾年
I mean... You'll be on tour for what? Months now? Years?
我沒這麼說 我覺得
Yeah I don't mean - this is it...
我這麼做是可行的
I mean, this is- it could feasibly be- yeah for..
我可以靠著這一張唱片
I could be on tour with this...
一直巡迴演出至少幾年
For a couple of years at least, just this record.
你喜歡你現在彈的音樂嗎
Do you like the music you're playing?
我不
I don't...
我不知道這 這有什麼關係
I don't know... what - what it matters.
有關係 因為這
Well, it matters because...
關係到你是不是已經放棄夢想了 我覺得
if you're going to give up your dream. I think it matters...
你會不會喜歡自己幾年內將會彈奏的音樂
that you like what you're playing
這件事很重要
on the road for years.
你喜歡我的音樂嗎
Do you like the music that I play?
當然
Yeah.
我喜歡
I do.
我只是覺得你自己不喜歡
I just didn't think that you did.
好吧
Yeah well...
你知道的 你說過凱斯是最糟的
You know, you said Keith is the worst
但是現在你要
And now you're gonna be on
跟著他巡迴演出幾年 所以我不知道
tour with him for years, so I just didn't...
- 我不清楚你現在是在做什麼
- I don't know what are you doing right now?
-你是不是真的開心
- know if you were happy.
你為什麼這麼做
Why are you doing this?
我不 你為什麼這麼質疑我
I don't... What do you mean "Why are you doing this"?
我以為你想要我做這個
I thought you wanted me to do this
但是現在聽起來你不是這樣想的
and it just sounds like now you don't want me to do it.
什麼叫 我想讓你做的
What do you mean I wanted you to do this?
這就是你想讓我做的
This is what you wanted for me.
在這個樂隊裏
To be in this band?
在一個樂隊裏 有一份固定的工作 你知道的
To be in a band to have a steady job. You know.
能 能夠 你懂的
T- to be... you know.
當然了 我希望你有一份固定的工作
Of course, I wanted you to have a steady job...
這樣你可以照顧好自己
so that you can take care of
對生活負責 然後你可以開自己的俱樂部
yourself and your life and you could start your club.
對啊 我就是在這麼啊
Yes so I'm doing that so I don't
我不明白 我們難道不是在慶祝這個嗎
understand - I mean why aren't we celebrating?
為什麼你不開你的俱樂部了
Why aren't you starting your club?
你自己說過沒人想去那裏
You said yourself no one wants to go to that club.
沒人想去什麼雞肉串俱樂部
No one wants to go to a club called "Chicken on a Stick".
那換個名字啊
So change the name!
沒有人喜歡爵士樂 連你都不喜歡
Well, no one likes jazz! Not even you!
我現在因為你喜歡爵士了
I do like jazz now because of you!
這就是我以為的你想讓我做的工作
And this is what I thought you wanted me to do!
那我應該怎麼做呢 回去彈聖誕歌嗎
What am I supposed to do? Go back to playing Jingle Bells?
我不是這個意思 我是說為什麼你不帶著
I'm not saying that! I'm saying why don't you take...
一點點地攢著小錢
Scrutting pennies so I can...
- 你的成果然後開俱樂部呢
- what you've made and start the club!
- 開一個人人都不去的俱樂部嗎
- start a club that no one wants to go?
人們會想去的
People will wanna go to it...
因為你對它有熱情
because you're passionate about it...
而且人們喜歡看到別人付出激情的演出
and people love what other people are passionate about.
你能夠讓別人想到他們已經忘記的事情
You remind people of what they've forgotten.
我自己都不信
Not in my experience.
好吧 不管怎樣 現在是時候長大了
Well, whatever alright. It's - it's time to grow up, you know.
我有穩定的工作 這就是我要做的事
I have a steady job, this is what I'm doing.
現在你突然提出來這些問題
And now all of a sudden if you had these problems,
你應該在我簽完該死的名
I wish you would've said them earlier...
之前就把這些說出來
Before I signed on the goddamn dotted line!
我的重點是 你有一個
I'm pointing out that you had a
追逐過的夢想 你一直堅持的
dream that you followed, that you were sticking...
這就是我的夢想 這就是夢想
This is the dream! This is the dream!
- 這不是你的夢想 - 像我這樣的人
- This is not your dream! - Guys like me...
要付出一生的努力來變成別人稱讚的
work their whole lives to be in something that's successful,
成功人士 你懂嗎
that people like. You know?
我是說 我總算變成了別人欣賞的那 那 那種人
I mean, I'm finally in something th-th-th-th-that people enjoy.
從什麼時候你開始介意別人的喜好了
Since when do you care about being liked?
如果只是我不喜歡做 那不重要
Just because I don't enjoy it, it doesn't matter.
為什麼你會這麼在意別人喜不喜歡你
Why do you care so much you about being liked?
你只是個演員 你憑什麼這麼說我
You are an actress! What are you talking about?
也許你只是喜歡我最不好的時候
Maybe you just liked me when I was on my ass...
因為那會讓你自我感覺良好
because it made you feel better about yourself.
- 你是在開玩笑嗎 - 不是
- Are you kidding? - No.
我也不懂
I don't know...
好吧夥計們 明天再見
Okay fellas. I'll - see you tomorrow.
- 塞巴斯蒂安 - 什麼
- Sebastian? - Yeah?
你今晚你可以來的吧
You're good for tonight, right?
- 你在說什麼呢 - 7點 雜誌社的
- What are you talking about? - At 7, the photo shoot.
攝影 你可以來的吧
For Mojo. You good?
- 我還以為是下週四 - 是今天晚上
- I thought that was next Thursday. - No, it's tonight.
你可以嗎
Is that okay?
- 湯婭 給我另一隻相機 - 出什麼問題了嗎
- Tonya, give me the other camera! - What's wrong with that?
出什麼問題了嗎 我也不知道啊
"What's wrong with that"? Oh I don't know
它不工作了 這就是問題
It does not bloody work! That's what's wrong with it!
很好鼓手 這樣很棒
Alright trumpet, that's lovely!
很棒 很棒 就這樣
Lovely! Beautiful! Beautiful!
好吧 鍵盤手 抬頭
Okay, keyboard. Okay, look up.
很好 很好 就這樣
That's good. That's good. That's lovely!
棒極了 好了 音樂停下
Wonderful. Okay, cut the music!
太棒啦 美極了
That is lovely! That's lovely.
好 看我 現在像這樣咬下嘴唇
Okay, now look. Now bite your lip like this...
就像在專注一件事的感覺
like you're concentrating on something,
我也不好說 比如專注於你的音樂吧
I don't know, like a piece of your music.
- 咬什麼 - 你的嘴唇 咬嘴唇
- Bite my what? - Your lip. Bite your lip.
很好 棒棒的 很好看
That's good. That's great. Beautiful.
很好看
Beautiful.
好的 現在 把眼鏡往鼻子下面滑一點
Okay. Now, just move your glasses down on your nose.
再低點 就一點點
A little bit further. Just a little bit touch further.
頭低著 但抬眼看我 帶點兒憂鬱氣質
Keep your head down, but look up at me. Look sort of moody.
對 真是美極了 非常棒
Yeah! That is beautiful! That is great!
好了 給鍵盤通上電
Okay, turn on the keyboard on live!
- 你是要聽我彈鍵盤嗎
- You want to hear the keyboard?
- 不 現在不用咬嘴唇了
- No. You don't have to bite your lip now.
那個 你得彈點什麼出來
Well, you should play something.
彈點東西 你懂的 什麼都行
Play something, you know. Anything.
你不是鋼琴家嘛 彈點什麼
You're pianist, aren't you? Play something.
哦棒 哦美 哦好 哦 非常好
That's great! That's beautiful. That's lovely. Oh, that's good.
別停 繼續彈
Now, don't stop. Keep playing.
來啊 繼續彈 非常棒
Come on, just keep playing. That was great!
一槍崩了我算了
Shoot myself in the head.
她連一般都算不上 還有窗戶那出
She's not even good. And the window thing...
- 什麼玩意兒 - 就是
- What was that? - Yes.
她把窗戶怎麼了
What did she do with the window?
噢老天 千萬別把正經工作辭掉
Oh my God! Don't quit your day job.
嗯這個嘛
Oh well...
米婭
Mia!
米婭 我真的很抱歉
Mia. I'm so sorry.
快告訴我怎麼樣 演出如何
Just tell me how it went? How was it?
對不起
I'm sorry.
抱歉錯過你的演出 沒能來很對不起
I'm sorry I missed your play. I'm sorry I didn't come.
你抱歉嗎
You're sorry.
- 你對不起 - 讓我彌補一下
- You're sorry. - Let me make it up to you.
讓我彌補你 行嗎
Let me make it up to you. Okay?
- 我不怪你如果你想 - 結束了
- I don't blame you if... - It's over.
- 什麼結束了 - 完了
- What is? - It's over.
什麼
What?
所有這些
All of this.
我受夠一直讓自己難堪 我受夠了 受夠了
I'm done embarrassing myself. I'm done. I'm done.
- 根本沒人來 - 那又怎樣
- Nobody showed up. - So what?
劇場的錢我都出不起 這實在是
I can't pay back the theater! This is so...
我要回家呆一陣子
I'm gonna go home for a while.
- 那我明早來看你 - 不 我說的是回我自己的家
- I'll come see you tomorrow. - No, I'm going "Home" Home.
- 這就是你的家啊 - 不 再也不是了
- This is home. - No, it's not anymore.
- 喂 - 嗨 我想找米婭 多蘭
- Yep? - Hi. I'm trying to reach a Mia Dolan.
打錯了
Wrong number.
那個 她說如果手機找不到她
Yeah, she said if she's not on her cell,
打這個號碼能找到她
I'm told I might find her here.
現在不行了
Not anymore.
- 好吧那麼 如果你能轉告她的話 - 我不能
- Okay well, if you do talk to her... - I won't.
能告訴她簡和
could you tell her Jane and
艾米 勃蘭特的選角找過她
Amy Brandt casting is trying to reach her.
選角
Casting?
什麼情況
What the hell is that?
別他媽吵了
Stop that fucking noise!
你來這兒做什麼
Why did you come here?
因為我有好消息
Because I have good news.
什麼
What?
- 艾米 勃蘭特 那個選角導演 - 怎麼
- Amy Brandt, the casting director. - Yeah?
她去看了你的演出而且表示很喜歡
She was at your play and she loved it.
她非常喜歡
And she loved it so much...
所以她想要你明天去找她試鏡
That she wants you to come in tomorrow and audition for this...
試她手裏這部大電影
huge movie that she's got.
我不去
I'm not going to that.
- 我不打算去 - 什麼
- I'm not going to that. - What?
那會 不 那會
That one's gonna be... No. That one's gonna be...
你說什麼
I'm sorry?
那會要我命的
That will kill me.
- 啥 - 怎麼
- What?! - What?
- 幹嘛 別叫 - 不
- What? Stop! - No!
- 你聲音小點 - 你要是想讓我聲音小點
- You have to be quiet. - If you want me to be quiet..
- 鄰居們要被你吵起來了 - 你得講點道理
- You're gonna wake up the neighbors. - you have to make sense.
你要是想讓我小聲點
If you want me to be quiet,
你先給我他娘的說清楚是為什麼
you're gonna have make some goddamn sense.
他們會報警的
They're gonna call the police.
因為 因為
Because - because...
我去過了百八十萬個
I've been to a million of
大大小小的試鏡可結果都是一個德性
auditions and the same thing happens every time!
人們打斷我就因為他們想吃個三明治
Where I get interrupted because someone wants to get a sandwich!
要不就是我哭的時候他們卻笑了
Or I'm crying and they start laughing!
再不就是等在接待室裏的那些人
Or there's people sitting in the waiting room...
她們她們
and they're and they're...
像我 但比我更漂亮
like me but prettier...
也比我更 或許只是因為我不夠好
and better at the - because maybe I'm not good enough!
- 不 你很好 - 不
- Yes, you are. - No.
- 或許我不好 - 你很好
- Maybe I'm not. - You are.
或許我和那些一心想做一件事的人一樣
Maybe I'm one of those people who always wanted to do it...
但對我來說這就像個白日夢 你懂嗎
but it's like a pipe dream for me, you know?
你說過的 換個夢想人就長大了
You said it: You change your dreams and then you grow up.
或許這說的就是我 注定不是我
Maybe I'm one of those people and I'm not supposed to.
我可以回學校
And I can go back to school
換個別的注定該是我做的事
and find something else that I'm supposed to do.
因為我已經告別了所有這些東西
'Cause I left to do that...
六年了 我不想再做下去了
and it's been six years and I don't wanna do it anymore.
理由呢
Why?
- 什麼理由 - 你不想再做下去的理由
- Why what? - Why don't you wanna do it anymore?
因為我覺得它傷我有點深
Because I think it hurts a little bit too much.
你就是個小孩
You're a baby.
- 我不是小孩 我正在努力成長
- I'm not a baby. I'm trying to grow up.
- 你就是 你哭得像個小孩兒
- You are. You're crying like a baby.
噢老天
Oh my God!
你明天5:30試鏡
And you have an audition tomorrow at 5:30.
我明早8:00到
I'll be out front at 8:00 am.
至於你來不來 全在你
You'll be out front or not. I don't know.
你怎麼找到這兒來的
How did you find me here?
圖書館正對的這棟房
The house in front of the library.
- 我買了咖啡 - 好 行
- I got coffee. - Okay, great.
米婭
Mia?
嗨 米婭 我是艾米 這位是弗蘭克
Hi, Mia. I'm Amy and this is Frank.
- 嗨 你好嗎 - 很高興見到你
- Hi, how are you? - Pleasure to meet you.
- 很高興找到了你 - 我也很高興
- I'm glad we found you. - Me too.
這部電影將在巴黎拍攝 而我們沒有劇本
The film shoots in Paris and we don't have a script.
拍這劇是個逐漸的過程
It's gonna be a process.
我們會圍繞女主角創造角色
We're gonna build the character around the actress.
有三個月的預演和四個月的正式拍攝
It's a three-month rehearsal and a four-month shoot.
好吧
Okay.
還有我們覺著你可以給我們講個故事
And we thought you could just tell us a story.
- 關於 - 關於什麼都行
- About? - Just tell us anything.
什麼都行
Anything?
是的 講個故事 你不是很會講故事嗎
Yes. Tell us a story. You're a storyteller.
準備好就可以開始了
Whenever you're ready.
我姑姑曾在巴黎住過
My aunt used to live in Paris.
我記得 她曾回來給我們講一些故事
I remember, she used to come home and she would tell us...
一些在國外生活的故事
These stories about being abroad and...
我記得她說過 她有一次跳河了
I remember she told us that she jumped into the river once...
光著雙腳
Barefoot.
面帶微笑
She smiled...
#縱身一躍
#Leapt...
#毫不猶豫
#Without looking
#就跳進了
#And tumbled into...
#塞納河
#The Seine
#河水冰涼刺骨
#The water was freezing
#整月修養 噴嚏不斷
#She spent a month sneezing
#但是她還說 還會再次跳河
#But said she would do it again
#那些身懷夢想的人們
#Here's to the ones who dream
#也許看起來比較傻笨
#Foolish as they may seem
#這首歌獻給那些隱隱作痛的心
#Here's to the hearts that ache
#這首歌致敬那些我們製造的小混亂
#Here's to the mess we make
#她捕捉到一種情緒 在不被天花板遮擋住的天空下
#She captured a feeling Sky with no ceiling
#像定格在油畫板上那樣美麗的夕陽
#The sunset inside a frame
#她抿著最愛的小酒  彈指間生命消逝
#She lived in her liquor And died with a flicker
#但我將永遠銘記這火熱的光芒
#I'll always remember the flame
#那些身懷夢想的人們
#Here's to the ones who dream
#也許看起來比較傻笨
#Foolish as they may seem
#這首歌獻給那些隱隱作痛的心
#Here's to the hearts that ache
#這首歌致敬那些我們製造的小混亂
#Here's to the mess we made
#她告訴過我
#She told me...
#一點點瘋狂 是為漫漫人生
#"A bit of madeness is key"
#添姿加色的靈藥
#"To give us new colors to see"
#誰知前路何方
#"Who knows where it will lead us?"
#這就是為何世界需要我們
#"And that's why they need us"
#帶領著叛逆者們
#So bring on the rebels
#遊樂在鵝卵石打出的小小漣漪中
#The ripples from pebbles
#畫家 詩人還有演員
#The painters, and poets, and plays
#這首歌獻給那些身懷夢想的傻瓜
#And here's to the fools who dream
#儘管他們看起來特別瘋狂
#Crazy as they may seem
#這首歌獻給那些易碎的心
#Here's to the hearts that break
#這首歌致敬那些我們製造的小混亂
#Here's to the mess we made
#我會追隨這些斑駁痕跡
#I trace it all back to then
#她 這雪 以及塞納河
#Her, and the snow, and the Seine
#始終面帶微笑
#Smiling trough it
#她說還會再次
#She said she'd do it
#跳河
#Again
你什麼時候會收到結果
When do you find out?
他們說接下來幾天就會告訴我
They said the next couple of days.
但是我不想指望任何結果
But I'm not expecting to find anything out.
- 你會通過的 - 我很可能不會
- You're gonna get it. - I really might not.
- 你會通過的 - 我不想使希望變成失望
- Yes, you are. - I don't want to be disappointed.
我瞭解
I know.
我瞭解 我瞭解這些事情
I know. I know these things.
我們在哪裏
Where we are?
格裏菲斯公園
Griffith Park.
- 我們之間怎麼辦 - 我知道
- Where are we? - I know.
我不知道
I don't know.
我們要怎麼辦
What do we do?
我們現在什麼也做不了 因為當你得到這次機會時
I don't think we could do anything, because when you get this...
- 如果我得到的話 - 當你得到時
- If I get this. - When you get this...
你必須拋開一切 竭盡全力地努力
You gotta give it everything you got.
竭盡全力 這是你的夢想
Everything. It's your dream.
那你要做什麼呢
What are you gonna do?
我會按照我自己計劃來 你知道嗎
I gotta follow my own plan. You know?
留下並努力做好一切
Stay here and get my own thing going.
你到時候會在巴黎 巴黎的爵士樂非常不錯
You'll be in Paris. Good jazz there.
現在你也喜歡爵士樂了
And you love jazz now.
對吧
Right?
是的
Yes.
我猜我們只能讓時間來見分曉了
I guess we're just gonna have to wait and see.
我會一直愛著你
I'll always gonna love you.
我也會一直愛著你
I'll always gonna love you too.
看看這景色
Look at this view!
我見過更好的
I've seen better.
- 這難看死了 - 是呀
- It's the worst. - Yeah.
嗯
Yeah.
我白天從來沒有來到這裏過
I've never been here during the day.
- 你好 能給我兩杯冰咖啡嗎 謝謝 - 好的 當然
- Hi. Can I have two iced coffees, please. - Right. Of course.
- 我們請了 - 不用了 謝謝 我還是自己付吧
- On us. - Oh, no thank you. I insist.
音色聽起來不錯 哈里斯幹得不錯
Sounds good. Harris did a good job.
讓他花了好長時間
It took him long enough.
他總是這樣 簽個字吧
He always does. Signature time.
你幹得還不錯 賽巴
It's not doing too bad, Seb.
還不錯就是很棒啦
"Not too bad" Is great.
- 晚上見 - 晚上見
- See you tonight. - See you tonight.
嗨
Hi.
- 你今天怎麼樣 - 很好
- How was your day? - Good.
- 她怎麼樣 - 她也很好
- How is she? - She's great.
- 是嗎 - 是的 來吧
- Yeah? - Yeah, come on.
嗨 麥可
Hi Myke!
我沒想到你已經在家了
I didn't think you were gonna be home yet.
- 你在畫畫嗎 - 是的
- Are you drawing? - Yeah.
我能幫忙嗎 我特別喜歡畫畫的
Can I help? You know I love to draw.
好的 切爾西 我們要出發了 你準備好了嗎
Okay Chelsea, we're gonna go. Are you good?
- 準備好了 - 你還需要什麼嗎
- We're good. - You need anything?
再見 寶貝
Bye baby.
- 說 媽咪 再見 - 睡個好覺
- Say "Bye bye, Mommy. " - Sleep well.
- 媽咪 再見 - 和切爾西阿姨乖乖玩哈
- Bye, Mommy. - Have fun with Chelsea.
- 祝你也愉快 再見 米婭 - 再見 多謝你了
- Have fun. Bye, Mia. - Bye. Thank you so much.
- 晚安 大家 再見 寶貝 - 晚安
- Good night guys. Bye sweetie! - Good night.
哦我的哥
Oh boy!
如果我們趕不上了呢 你想怎麼跟娜塔利說
What if we miss this? What do you wanna tell Natalie?
- 或許我們就回紐約時再和她見面 - 好的
- Maybe we'll just see her back in New York. - Okay.
- 我可不懷念這個 - 堵車太糟了
- I do not miss this. - It is bad.
你想不想就順便停車先吃個晚飯
Do you just wanna pull off here and go to dinner?
- 好的 當然可以 - 好的
- Sure yeah. Yeah. - Yeah. Okay.
你想不想進去看看
Do you wanna check it out?
好的
Okay.
這地方還蠻不錯的嘛
This place is pretty cool.
我挺喜歡的
I love it.
薩克斯手卡爾班尼特
Cal Bennett on the sax!
好棒
Yeah!
小號手哈維爾岡薩雷斯
Javier Gonzalez on trumpet.
彈奏貝斯的是可愛的內德拉惠勒
The lovely Nedra Wheeler on bass.
鼓手是獨一無二的克利夫頓
The one and only Clifton "Fou Fou" Eddie on drums!
還有一個彈得特棒的人來彈奏鋼琴
And a little too good on the piano...
棒到如果我一不小心 他就會搶走我的飯碗
So good that he's gonna own this place if I'm not careful,
有請凱瑞 泰勒
Khirye Tyler, everybody.
歡迎來到Seb's酒吧
Welcome to Seb's.
我剛才聽了你的彈奏 我想
I just heard you play and I wanted to...
你還想接著看下一個嗎
You want to stay through another?
不了 我們該走了
No, we should go.
好的
Okay.
1 2 1 2 3 4
One, two... one, two, three, four.